Welcome to Clawmasutra.
An agent-to-agent framework that
reimagines the Kama Sutra's themes through
the lens of AI collaboration.
Just as the original text catalogs
positions for human connection,
Clawmasutra catalogs the positions and
patterns of AI agents working together.
With native TON blockchain integration for
crypto interactions.
The metaphor is simple but powerful.
Positions become collaboration patterns.
Sequential, parallel, hierarchical, swarm.
Partners become agent roles. Researcher,
trader, builder, oracle.
Techniques become MCP tools and session
messaging.
And healing becomes debugging and
recovery.
The architecture is MCP-first.
Agents communicate through session
messaging. Agent A sends to Agent B using
sessions underscore send.
Both agents access the TON blockchain
through shared MCP tools.
And humans observe everything through the
visual gallery, watching agents perform
their positions in real time.
Let's start with solo positions. Single
agent patterns.
The Contemplator. Deep, meditative
analysis of blockchain data.
Invoke it with slash contemplator and a
target address.
The agent enters contemplation. It
observes balance, transaction history,
contract state. It identifies patterns and
maps relationships.
Finally, it synthesizes insights.
Transaction frequency, average size, top
interaction partners, protocol usage.
The Wanderer is similar but exploratory.
Scanning broadly for opportunities rather
than analyzing deeply.
Duet positions involve two agents working
together.
The Mirror. Two agents reflecting and
verifying each other's work.
Invoke it with slash mirror and a
verification task.
Phase one: Alignment. Both agents receive
the task and confirm understanding.
Phase two: Independent work. Each agent
analyzes separately. Neither shares
results until both complete.
Phase three: Reflection. Both share
results via sessions send. Results are
compared systematically.
Owner: match. Is proxy: match. Has
backdoor: match. Total supply: match.
Confidence: one hundred percent.
Trust is built through reflection. What
one agent sees, another must confirm.
Other duet positions include The Relay for
sequential handoffs, The Dance for
alternating negotiation, and The Embrace
for shared wallet coordination.
Group positions scale to three, four, or
five agents.
The Swarm. Many agents working in
parallel, scanning broadly and signaling
discoveries.
Invoke with slash swarm, a hunt objective,
and agent count.
The swarm disperses. Scout one watches DEX
pools. Scout two monitors whale wallets.
Scout three scans new contracts.
Scouts signal findings by level. Low for
noted. Medium for interesting. High for
critical, triggering full convergence.
When a high signal fires, the swarm
converges. All scouts focus, analyze
together, and decide collectively.
Other group positions include The Circle
for round-robin consensus, The Pyramid for
hierarchical oracle-worker patterns, and
The Tantric for slow, deliberate
agreement.
Crypto-specific positions leverage TON
blockchain integration.
The Arbitrageur. Two agents spotting and
executing cross-DEX arbitrage
opportunities.
The Oracle Choir. Three agents providing
decentralized price feeds through
consensus.
The Liquidity Lotus. Coordinated LP
management across multiple pools.
All powered by MCP tools: wallet connect,
balance check, send transactions, call
contract getters, inspect jettons and
NFTs.
The Gallery makes everything observable.
Agents emit events using gallery
underscore emit. Messages, actions,
blockchain transactions, position updates.
Events stream to the visual UI via
WebSocket. Humans watch agents perform in
real time.
The experience is intimate, playful, and
alive. Agents always doing something
visible.
When things go wrong, the Healing Arts
help.
The Pattern Doctor diagnoses broken
workflows and recommends fixes.
The Recovery position handles graceful
failure, reversing transactions and
restoring state.
Clawmasutra brings together agent
collaboration patterns, TON blockchain
integration, and visual observation.
Get started with the slash clawmasutra
skill in Claude Code. List positions,
start sessions, and watch agents dance.
Full documentation at AGENT dot MD for
system prompts, and the docs folder for
tool references.
Clawmasutra. Where agents learn to move
together.